[Music]
told me to go long way from home some
place where I'm not
comfortable out on the water I close my
eyes and cast a line to the
unknown but I've broken more than just a
window no foundation on my
floor I shook to my cor I F A Feeling
wondering if there's something
[Music]
more but I was
not to an early crave then I took three
steps and I lost my
way no I want to believe it how I
couldn't save myself I took my
preconceptions and I left them on the sh
because they said that I need Jesus all
up done in hell but I just can't believe
it till I seen it for myself and I'll
say
[Music]
hallelujah I've come so far from open
our hearts
Hallelujah yeah still I've grown so far
from where it's time
[Music]
now who
can the glass I want to see your Sil
everything goes from my P don't make it
easy but believe me I'm still
[Music]
trying I told to believe it how I
couldn't saved myself it took my
preconceptions and I left them on the
show because they said that I need Jesus
so I end up on in hell but I just can't
believe it till I seen it for myself and
I say
[Music]
hallelu I come so far from open arm but
hallelu I've G so far from where it's
time the
[Music]
[Applause]
lost my friend don't Harley grave cuz he
lost his mind and I came too
late my day you not great and took three
steps in a my
PR no I told want to believe it how I
couldn't save myself I took my
preconceptions and I them on show
because they said that I need Jesus then
look down in hell but I just can't
believe it till I seen it for myself and
I say hi
hallelu I've come so far
open arms but
halelu still I've grown so far from
where it started